<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<featureModel>
	<properties>
		<graphics key="autolayoutconstraints" value="false"/>
		<graphics key="legendautolayout" value="true"/>
		<graphics key="showconstraints" value="true"/>
		<graphics key="showshortnames" value="false"/>
		<graphics key="layout" value="horizontal"/>
		<graphics key="showcollapsedconstraints" value="true"/>
		<graphics key="legendhidden" value="false"/>
		<graphics key="layoutalgorithm" value="1"/>
	</properties>
	<struct>
		<and abstract="true" mandatory="true" name="Multi-artefact Management">
			<description>
				High-level feature for managing multiple artefacts within a dynamic, heterogeneous data ecosystem.
				This feature addresses the growing complexity and heterogeneity of data models and schemas, focusing on structural, semantic, and similarity-based differences across domains.
			</description>
			<feature abstract="true" mandatory="true" name="Operations">
				<description>Defines the operations or actions that can be performed on multiple artefacts, ensuring the ability to manipulate artefacts effectively.</description>
			</feature>
			<feature abstract="true" mandatory="true" name="Artefacts">
				<description>
					Refers to the sources of the artefacts being compared, specifically the models or schemas that are used in the comparison process.
					Artefacts can come from diverse domains and abstraction levels, such as models in Model-Driven Engineering (MDE) or schemas in database systems.
				</description>
			</feature>
			<feature abstract="true" mandatory="true" name="Multi-modal">
				<description>
					Addresses the paradigm of handling multiple, diverse model of Heterogeneity ie. Homogeneous or Heterogeneous  .
					This feature is concerned with the interaction where each model may have different constraints, rules, or semantics.
				</description>
			</feature>
			<feature abstract="true" mandatory="true" name="Approaches">
				<description>
					Covers a wide range of ML/AI-based techniques used to address the challenges of model and schema comparison.
					The approaches also includes Hybrid approaches with classical ones.
				</description>
			</feature>
		</and>
	</struct>
</featureModel>
