<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<featureModel>
	<properties>
		<graphics key="autolayoutconstraints" value="false"/>
		<graphics key="legendautolayout" value="true"/>
		<graphics key="showconstraints" value="true"/>
		<graphics key="showshortnames" value="false"/>
		<graphics key="layout" value="horizontal"/>
		<graphics key="showcollapsedconstraints" value="true"/>
		<graphics key="legendhidden" value="false"/>
		<graphics key="layoutalgorithm" value="1"/>
	</properties>
	<struct>
		<and abstract="true" mandatory="true" name="Operations">
			<description>Represents the operations that can be applied to the comparison and integration of models and schemas. This includes matching, mapping, and alignment processes.</description>
			<and abstract="true" mandatory="true" name="Matching">
				<description>Defines the process of identifying correspondences between models or schemas.</description>
				<and abstract="true" mandatory="true" name="Matching Unit">
					<description>Represents the different units or approaches used in the matching process.</description>
					<or abstract="true" mandatory="true" name="Structural">
						<description>Focuses on matching based on the structure of models or schemas. Select exactly one approach.</description>
						<feature name="Graph">
							<description>Matching based on graph structures in the models or schemas.</description>
						</feature>
						<feature name="Syntactic / Linguistic">
						<description>Matching based on the syntactic or linguistic aspects of the models or schemas.</description>
					</feature>
					<feature name="Tree/Textual">
					<description>Matching based on tree structures or textual representations.</description>
				</feature>
			</or>
			<or abstract="true" mandatory="true" name="Semantic">
				<description>Focuses on matching based on the semantic meaning of the data. Select exactly one approach.</description>
				<feature name="Instance-based">
					<description>Matching based on instances or data objects in the models or schemas.</description>
				</feature>
				<feature name="DSL-Driven">
					<description>Matching based on domain-specific languages (DSLs) used in the models or schemas.</description>
				</feature>
				<feature name="Knowledge Graph">
					<description>Matching based on knowledge graph structures.</description>
				</feature>
				<feature name="Ontology-based">
					<description>Matching based on ontologies and their relationships within models or schemas.</description>
				</feature>
			</or>
			<alt abstract="true" mandatory="true" name="Similarity">
				<description>Focuses on matching based on the similarity of elements in the models or schemas. Select exactly one approach.</description>
				<feature name="Element">
					<description>Matching based on the similarity of individual elements in the models or schemas.</description>
				</feature>
				<feature name="Name">
					<description>Matching based on the similarity of names in the models or schemas.</description>
				</feature>
				<feature name="Value">
					<description>Matching based on the similarity of values in the models or schemas.</description>
				</feature>
			</alt>
		</and>
	</and>
	<feature abstract="true" mandatory="true" name="Mapping">
		<description>Defines the process of establishing relationships or transformations between different models or schemas. Mapping depends on the Matching stage.</description>
	</feature>
	<feature abstract="true" mandatory="true" name="Alignment">
		<description>Defines the process of aligning models or schemas based on common attributes, structures, or semantics. Alignment depends on the Mapping and Matching stages.</description>
	</feature>
	<and abstract="true" mandatory="true" name="Execution Context">
		<description>Defines the environment and circumstances under which the matching, mapping, or alignment process occurs. It describes when and where the operations are executed.</description>
		<alt abstract="true" mandatory="true" name="Storage">
			<description>Describes where the data related to the matching, mapping, or alignment process is kept.</description>
			<feature name="Transient">
				<description>Temporary storage that is discarded after the operation is complete.</description>
			</feature>
			<alt abstract="true" name="Persistent">
				<description>Long-term storage where data is kept even after the operation is complete.</description>
				<feature name="Cloud-based">
					<description>Data is stored in cloud-based environments for easy access and scalability.</description>
				</feature>
				<feature name="Hard-drive">
					<description>Data is stored locally on a hard drive for secure and permanent storage.</description>
				</feature>
				<feature name="In-memory">
					<description>Data is stored in-memory for fast access during operation execution.</description>
				</feature>
			</alt>
		</alt>
		<or abstract="true" mandatory="true" name="Invocation">
			<description>Defines how often the matching, mapping, or alignment process is executed.</description>
			<feature name="Once">
				<description>The process is executed only one time, typically for a single comparison.</description>
			</feature>
			<feature name="Repeated">
				<description>The process is executed multiple times, typically for iterative or ongoing operations.</description>
			</feature>
		</or>
	</and>
</and>
</struct>
</featureModel>
