<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<featureModel>
	<properties>
		<graphics key="autolayoutconstraints" value="false"/>
		<graphics key="legendautolayout" value="true"/>
		<graphics key="showconstraints" value="true"/>
		<graphics key="showshortnames" value="false"/>
		<graphics key="layout" value="horizontal"/>
		<graphics key="showcollapsedconstraints" value="true"/>
		<graphics key="legendhidden" value="false"/>
		<graphics key="layoutalgorithm" value="1"/>
	</properties>
	<struct>
		<and abstract="true" mandatory="true" name="Operations::Mapping">
			<description>The "Mapping" feature defines how identified correspondences between models or schemas should be transformed, translated, or unified. It focuses on converting data or structures from one model to another.</description>
			<and abstract="true" mandatory="true" name="Commonalities">
				<description>Describes the general ways in which mapping relationships are handled, focusing on unification and relationship handling across models.</description>
				<alt abstract="true" mandatory="true" name="Representation">
					<description>Defines how the mapping relationships are expressed or what operations are involved in the mapping process.</description>
					<feature name="Complement-based">
						<description>Defines mappings based on what's missing or what needs to be added to one model to align with another.</description>
					</feature>
					<or abstract="true" name="Traceability">
						<description>Ensures that links or records of how elements are mapped are maintained, aiding in debugging, impact analysis, and transformations.</description>
						<feature name="Merging">
							<description>Combines elements from different models into a single element in the target model.</description>
						</feature>
						<feature name="Weaving">
							<description>Creates connections between elements from different models without changing the models themselves.</description>
						</feature>
						<feature name="Decoration">
							<description>Adds extra information or annotations to elements, enriching the target model with data from the source.</description>
						</feature>
						<feature name="Transformation">
							<description>Converts the structure or data of elements from one model to another model's format.</description>
						</feature>
					</or>
				</alt>
				<or abstract="true" mandatory="true" name="Commonality Definition">
					<description>Specifies how mapping rules or logic are defined and applied during the mapping process.</description>
					<feature name="Predefined">
						<description>Mapping rules that are predefined by the system and fixed, not easily changed by the user.</description>
					</feature>
					<feature name="Implicit">
						<description>Mapping that is inferred automatically by the system, often based on conventions or assumptions.</description>
					</feature>
				</or>
			</and>
			<alt abstract="true" mandatory="true" name="Unification Architecture">
				<description>Defines the architecture for managing mappings across different models, describing how control and governance are organized.</description>
				<or abstract="true" name="Global View">
					<description>Describes different centralized approaches for managing mapping control across models.</description>
					<feature name="Centralised">
						<description>A single entity has control over the mapping process.</description>
					</feature>
					<feature name="Hierarchical">
						<description>Control is centralized but with levels, such as a central team with sub-teams managing mappings.</description>
					</feature>
					<feature name="Shared Central Authority">
						<description>Multiple entities jointly control the central authority for mapping (e.g., a committee).</description>
					</feature>
				</or>
				<or abstract="true" name="Federation">
					<description>Describes different decentralized approaches where multiple entities share control over mappings.</description>
					<feature name="Autonomous">
						<description>Each entity has full control over its correspondences, with no central coordination.</description>
					</feature>
					<feature name="Cooperative Agreement">
						<description>Entities agree on standards or protocols for interoperability but manage their own mappings.</description>
					</feature>
					<feature name="Delegation">
						<description>Entities delegate some control to a coordinating body for specific aspects of the mapping process.</description>
					</feature>
				</or>
			</alt>
		</and>
	</struct>
</featureModel>
